Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Kathryn and we have a very fun lesson for you today.
我是Kathryn，今天我们为大家准备了一堂非常有趣的课。
That's right.
没错。
We're going to talk about toys.
我们要聊聊玩具。
So we're going to actually take a look at a lot of different types of toys and we're
所以我们会看到很多不同类型的玩具，
going to be listening to a couple of commercials.
还会听几段广告。
That's right.
没错。
So we've got two children who are watching TV and they're listening to a number of different
有两个小孩在看电视，
commercials.
他们正在听几段不同的广告。
So we're going to learn about some of these very popular products in a moment.
我们马上就会了解一些非常受欢迎的产品。
Let's first listen to our dialogue.
先来听一下我们的对话。
Spongebob Squarepants will be right back after these brief messages.
海绵宝宝马上回来，广告之后见。
What's that on the horizon?
地平线上那是什么？
A pirate ship.
一艘海盗船。
Raid villages and find buried treasure with these new pirates Lego set.
用这套新的乐高海盗系列，袭击村庄、寻找宝藏。
Build the ship and decide who rules the sea.
搭建船只，决定谁统治海洋。
Har!
哈！
Cool!
酷！
Play-Doh sparkling brights precious gem press.
培乐多彩泥闪亮宝石压模机。
Make large colorful gems for you and your friends with five special molds.
用五个特殊模具，为你和朋友制作大颗彩色宝石。
Comes with a new sparkling brights Play-Doh compound in four new colors.
配有新的闪亮培乐多彩泥，四种新颜色。
Treasure chest sold separately.
宝箱需单独购买。
Wow mommy!
哇，妈妈！
Can I get that for my birthday?
我生日能买那个吗？
Wolverine, Jean Grey, Rogue and Professor X.
金刚狼、琴·葛蕾、罗刹女和X教授。
Collect all four of these special edition collectible X-Men action figures and decide
收集这四款特别版X战警可动人偶，
the future of the mutants in our world.
决定我们世界中变种人的未来。
No way!
不会吧！
I want Professor X!
我想要X教授！
The new collector's edition nursery rhymes porcelain dolls.
新款收藏版童谣瓷娃娃。
Little Bo Peep comes with her own shape and staff.
小波比带着自己的羊和牧羊杖。
Her clothes are made with the finest fabrics and real Italian lace.
她的衣服用最优质的面料和真正的意大利蕾丝制成。
And her face has been hand painted by our finest artists.
她的脸由我们最优秀的艺术家手工绘制。
Only $199.
仅售199美元。
Oh!
哦！
She's pretty!
她真漂亮！
I've never had a porcelain doll before.
我以前从没有过瓷娃娃。
I doubt mom and dad will get you that for your birthday.
我怀疑爸妈会不会给你买那个当生日礼物。
She costs a pretty penny.
她可不便宜。
Plus you'd most likely break her.
而且你很可能把她弄坏。
What is better than a board?
什么比棋盘更好？
What is better than one board game?
什么比一个棋盘游戏更好？
Three board games in one!
三个棋盘游戏合为一体！
Enjoy playing chess and checkers on this side of the board.
在棋盘这一面玩国际象棋和跳棋。
But if you're looking for some more fun, flip it and play the classic game of sorry.
但如果你想找更多乐趣，翻过来玩经典游戏“抱歉”。
That's ingenious!
太有创意了！
Why hasn't anyone thought of that before?
为什么以前没人想到这个？
Now you can take SpongeBob SquarePants wherever you go with the new SpongeBob SquarePants
现在你可以带着海绵宝宝去任何地方，
glow in the dark yo-yo.
用这款新的海绵宝宝夜光悠悠球。
And now, back to our show.
现在，回到我们的节目。
Alright we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So a lot of great toys and actually it's very popular that while maybe you're watching cartoons,
所以有很多很棒的玩具，实际上很常见的是，当你在看动画片时，
you get a lot of these commercials that are selling you all types of toys.
会看到很多推销各种玩具的广告。
Absolutely, because normally children watch cartoons and children like toys.
当然，因为通常孩子们看动画片，而孩子们喜欢玩具。
So it makes sense.
所以这很合理。
Exactly.
没错。
So why don't we take a look at six key words that we have for you on Language Takeaway.
那我们来看看“语言小贴士”环节中为大家准备的六个关键词吧。
Language Takeaway.
语言小贴士。
Okay Marco, so what's the first word we're looking at here today?
好的Marco，今天我们看的第一个词是什么？
Alright, we have actually a brand, a very famous type of toy.
好的，我们有一个品牌，一种非常著名的玩具。
They're called Legos.
它叫乐高。
Legos.
乐高。
So Lego, Legos.
所以是Lego，Legos。
So Legos are basically little pieces that you put together to build things.
乐高基本上就是一些小零件，你可以拼在一起搭建东西。
Yeah, they're like little blocks.
对，就像小积木块。
Okay, so when you see them, they don't look like anything.
好的，所以刚看到时，它们看起来没什么特别。
But as a child, you get to create anything you want.
但作为孩子，你可以创造任何你想要的东西。
So Legos have become very famous.
所以乐高变得非常有名。
They have like special types that you can recreate maybe a spaceship from Star Wars,
现在有各种特殊系列，比如你可以重现《星球大战》的宇宙飞船、
a pirate ship, a lot of different types now.
海盗船，很多不同的类型。
Okay, so the one in today's commercial is Pirate Legos.
好的，今天广告里的是海盗乐高。
So they're building a pirate ship.
所以他们正在搭建一艘海盗船。
Exactly, Legos.
没错，乐高。
Alright and the next toy that we have is also a proper noun.
好的，下一个玩具也是一个专有名词。
It's a brand and it's called Play-Doh.
它是一个品牌，叫培乐多。
Play-Doh.
培乐多。
Okay, so play like playing with something, playing basketball.
好的，play就像玩东西、打篮球。
But Play-Doh is...
但培乐多是……
It's like clay, right?
它就像黏土，对吧？
It's like clay, but it's made out of flour I think and you can shape it into anything
它就像黏土，但我觉得是用面粉做的，你可以把它捏成任何形状。
you want.
你想要的。
So when I was little, I used to make Play-Doh animals.
所以小时候，我经常用培乐多捏动物。
You know, you could make a ball and you make another ball and all of a sudden you have
你知道，你可以搓一个球，再搓一个球，然后突然就变成
a cow.
一头牛了。
Right.
对。
So it's a very soft texture type of a material that you can mold.
所以这是一种质地非常柔软、可以塑形的材料。
You can give it different shapes and that's what we call Play-Doh.
你可以给它不同的形状，这就是我们说的培乐多。
Obviously, as you say, it's safe for children.
显然，就像你说的，它对儿童是安全的。
I think it's made out of some flour.
我觉得它是用一些面粉做的。
Salt and flour.
盐和面粉。
And I think a lot of children sometimes eat this.
而且我觉得很多小孩有时候会吃这个。
So it's pretty safe for kids.
所以对小孩来说相当安全。
Right.
对。
So yeah, that's Play-Doh.
所以，这就是培乐多。
It's a proper noun and I guess everyone just calls it Play-Doh.
它是一个专有名词，我想大家都直接叫它培乐多。
So this is the toy that we're talking about.
这就是我们在讨论的玩具。
Now moving on, we're talking about the X-Men.
现在继续，我们来说说X战警。
Wolverine, Jean Grey, Rogue, Professor X, and all of these come in little statues that
金刚狼、琴·葛蕾、小淘气、X教授，这些角色都有小雕像，
we call action figures.
我们称之为可动人偶。
All right.
好的。
So what you're talking about here are obviously the X-Men, Marco.
所以你在这里说的显然是X战警，马可。
And X-Men, there are many different kinds of X-Men.
而X战警有很多不同的种类。
You have, like you said, Wolverine, who's maybe one of the most famous and Rogue.
就像你说的，有金刚狼，他可能是最有名的之一，还有小淘气。
But when you collect these little statues, these little dolls, they're called action
但当你收集这些小雕像、小玩偶时，它们被称为可动人偶。
figures.
人偶。
So figure is like a kind of doll.
所以figure就像是一种玩偶。
Right.
对。
So the X-Men is just an example.
所以X战警只是一个例子。
You have action figures of all sorts of cartoons or movies.
各种卡通或电影都有可动人偶。
Star Wars action figures are very popular.
星球大战的可动人偶非常受欢迎。
Or G.I.
或者G.I.
Joe action figures are very popular as well.
Joe的可动人偶也很受欢迎。
That's right.
没错。
So they're little toy statues that children play with.
所以它们是孩子们玩的小玩具雕像。
All right.
好的。
Moving on, now we have an adjective, a way to describe the X-Men.
继续，现在我们有一个形容词，用来描述X战警。
That's right.
没错。
X-Men, as you know, are not normal people.
X战警，如你所知，不是普通人。
They have special powers.
他们有特殊能力。
Some X-Men can fly.
有些X战警会飞。
Wolverine has animal abilities.
金刚狼有动物般的能力。
He can use his long claws.
他能用他的长爪子。
So these are mutants.
所以这些是变种人。
That means that they were humans, but something changed in them and it makes them have these
这意味着他们曾经是人类，但体内发生了某种变化，使他们拥有了这些
special powers.
特殊能力。
OK.
好的。
So a mutant is maybe a person that has special powers, like as you say, Wolverine and all
所以变种人可能是指有特殊能力的人，就像你说的金刚狼和所有
these types of X-Men.
这类X战警。
But I guess to, taking maybe a look at the verb mutate, that means...
但我想，也许看看动词mutate，它的意思是……
To change.
改变。
To change, right?
改变，对吧？
OK.
好的。
So to mutate is to change.
所以to mutate就是改变。
So we could say, I found a frog that had three legs.
所以我们可以说，我发现了一只三条腿的青蛙。
OK.
好的。
So it clearly mutated because normally frogs have like four legs.
所以它显然发生了变异，因为通常青蛙有四条腿。
Exactly.
正是。
You see that sometimes with chickens that maybe have two heads or something like this.
你有时会看到鸡有两个头或类似的情况。
These are mutants.
这些就是变种。
OK.
好的。
They have mutated.
它们发生了变异。
OK.
好的。
So that's a mutation.
所以那就是突变。
And now moving on to our dolls.
现在继续聊我们的玩偶。
They were talking about these beautiful porcelain dolls.
他们刚才在谈论那些漂亮的瓷娃娃。
OK.
好的。
So let's talk about porcelain because I think everyone knows what a doll is.
所以我们来说说瓷器，因为我觉得大家都知道玩偶是什么。
But porcelain is a special kind of doll, right?
但瓷器是一种特殊的玩偶，对吧？
Right.
对。
It's a material.
它是一种材料。
And usually you can find this material very commonly in your plates.
而且你通常能在盘子上常见到这种材料。
All right.
好的。
So it's not clear.
它不是透明的。
It's not glass.
它不是玻璃。
No.
不是。
It's colored.
它是有颜色的。
It's normally whitish and very, very fine, very pretty.
它通常是偏白色的，非常非常精细，非常漂亮。
So you call it porcelain.
所以你叫它瓷器。
I guess it's a type of ceramic, right?
我想它是一种陶瓷，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
OK.
好的。
So yeah, you have porcelain dolls.
所以，是的，你有瓷娃娃。
Many people also have very fine china that you call it, like dinner plates.
很多人也有非常精美的瓷器，你称之为，比如餐盘。
Or teacups.
或者茶杯。
And those are usually made of porcelain.
而那些通常是用瓷器做的。
All right.
好的。
And finally, they were talking about a game that has three games in one.
最后，他们在谈论一个三合一的游戏。
And one of the kids said, wow, that's ingenious.
其中一个孩子说，哇，这太巧妙了。
Ingenious.
巧妙。
This is a great word.
这是个很棒的词。
Makes you sound really fluent.
让你听起来很流利。
So ingenious basically means clever.
所以巧妙基本上就是聪明的意思。
Right.
对。
It's a really good idea.
这是个非常好的主意。
It's a very clever, good idea.
这是个非常聪明、好的主意。
So if something is ingenious, it's just, wow, it's very creative.
所以如果某样东西很巧妙，那就是，哇，非常有创意。
For example, I have a pair of gloves, but on the fingers, sometimes I can pull a cover
比如，我有一副手套，但在手指上，有时我可以拉一个盖子
over them and they turn into mittens.
盖住它们，它们就变成了连指手套。
I think it's ingenious.
我觉得这很巧妙。
You have gloves and mittens.
你既有分指手套又有连指手套。
I have gloves and mittens all the time.
我随时都有分指手套和连指手套。
All right.
好的。
So a lot of interesting words there.
所以那里有很多有趣的词。
A lot of specific toys and particularly brands that you may or may not know.
很多特定的玩具，特别是你可能知道也可能不知道的品牌。
But why don't we go back and listen to the dialogue again and we'll be back with Fluency
但我们为什么不回去再听一遍对话，然后我们会回来进行流利度
Builder.
构建环节。
Spongebob Squarepants will be right back after these brief messages.
海绵宝宝在这些简短消息后马上回来。
What's that on the horizon?
地平线上那是什么？
A pirate ship.
一艘海盗船。
Raid villages and find buried treasure with this new pirate's Lego set.
用这个新的海盗乐高套装袭击村庄并寻找埋藏的宝藏。
Build the ship and decide who rules the sea.
建造船只并决定谁统治海洋。
Arr.
啊。
Cool.
酷。
The new Play-Doh Sparkling Brights Precious Gem Press.
新的培乐多彩泥闪亮亮珍贵宝石压模机。
Make large colorful gems for you and your friends with five special molds.
用五个特殊模具为你和你的朋友制作大颗彩色宝石。
Comes with the new Sparkling Brights Play-Doh compound in four new colors.
配有新的闪亮亮彩泥材料，四种新颜色。
Treasure chest sold separately.
宝箱单独出售。
Wow, mommy, can I get that for my birthday?
哇，妈妈，我生日能要那个吗？
Wolverine, Jean Grey, Rogue, and Professor X.
金刚狼、琴·葛蕾、小淘气和X教授。
Collect all four of these special edition collectible X-Men action figures and decide
收集所有这四个特别版X战警可动人偶，并决定
the future of the mutants in our world.
我们世界中变种人的未来。
No way!
不会吧！
I want Professor X!
我想要X教授！
The new Collector's Edition Nursery Rhymes Porcelain Dolls.
新的收藏版童谣瓷娃娃。
Little Bo Peep comes with her own sheep and staff.
小波比带着她自己的羊和牧羊杖。
Her clothes are made with the finest fabrics and real Italian lace.
她的衣服是用最好的面料和真正的意大利蕾丝制成的。
And her face has been hand painted by our finest artists.
她的脸是由我们最优秀的艺术家手绘的。
Only $199.
仅售199美元。
Ooh, she's pretty.
哦，她真漂亮。
I've never had a porcelain doll before.
我以前从未有过瓷娃娃。
I doubt mom and dad will get you that for your birthday.
我怀疑爸妈会不会给你买那个当生日礼物。
She costs a pretty penny.
她可不便宜。
Plus, you'd most likely break her.
而且，你很可能把她弄坏。
What is better than a board?
什么比棋盘更好？
What is better than one board game?
什么比一个棋盘游戏更好？
Three board games in one!
三个棋盘游戏合而为一！
Enjoy playing chess and checkers on this side of the board.
在棋盘这一面享受下国际象棋和跳棋。
But if you're looking for some more fun, flip it and play the classic game of Sorry.
但如果你想找更多乐趣，翻过来玩经典的“抱歉”游戏。
That's ingenious!
那太巧妙了！
Why hasn't anyone thought of that before?
为什么以前没人想到这个？
Now you can take SpongeBob SquarePants wherever you go with the new SpongeBob SquarePants
现在你可以带着海绵宝宝去任何地方，用新的海绵宝宝
Glow in the Dark Yo-Yo.
夜光悠悠球。
And now, back to our show.
现在，回到我们的节目。
Okay, so the first phrase here in Fluency Builder is a really important one for anyone
好的，所以流利度构建中的第一个短语对任何
who's buying anything because you often see this phrase on packages or you hear it in
买东西的人来说都非常重要，因为你经常在包装上看到这个短语，或者在
commercials.
广告中听到它。
Right.
对。
As you saw in the Play-Doh commercial, the guy said, treasure chest sold separately.
就像你在培乐多彩泥广告中看到的，那个人说，宝箱单独出售。
Okay, sold separately.
好的，单独出售。
That means the treasure chest is not included.
这意味着宝箱不包含在内。
You have to buy it extra.
你必须额外购买。
As you say, you usually see it in packaging as well.
就像你说的，你通常在包装上也能看到。
Maybe you buy a toy car and at the bottom it will say, batteries sold separately.
也许你买一个玩具车，底部会写着，电池单独出售。
That means there are no batteries in the box.
这意味着盒子里没有电池。
You have to buy batteries extra.
你必须额外购买电池。
Exactly.
完全正确。
So that's what the phrase sold separately means.
所以这就是短语“单独出售”的意思。
It indicates that it's not included in the product that you are buying.
它表示它不包含在你购买的产品中。
Alright now moving on again to the action figures and the dolls.
好了，现在我们继续聊动作人偶和娃娃。
We saw this very interesting way of describing them.
我们看到了一个非常有趣的描述它们的方式。
For example, the action figure said, special edition collectible X-Men action figures.
比如，动作人偶上写着：特别版收藏级X战警动作人偶。
Okay, special edition.
好的，特别版。
This is really important and it's very common I think with special toys or action figures
这真的很重要，而且我觉得在特殊玩具、动作人偶甚至棒球卡中很常见。
or even baseball cards.
甚至棒球卡。
Special edition means that they're produced specially on one occasion, at one time.
特别版意味着它们是专门为某个场合、某个时间生产的。
They're not always produced.
它们不是一直生产的。
Right.
对。
So for example, if you have like you say, baseball cards or maybe action figures.
所以比如，像你说的棒球卡或动作人偶。
They're produced normally but then a limited amount, a special type of the same action
它们通常是批量生产的，但随后会生产有限数量、特殊类型的同款动作人偶。
figure will be produced.
会生产出来。
So that's a special edition or also commonly known as a collector's edition.
那就是特别版，也常被称为收藏版。
Alright so some people collect stamps, you know stamps for letters that you send.
好的，有些人收集邮票，就是寄信用的那种邮票。
And I know many countries like America offer special edition or collector's edition stamps.
我知道很多国家，比如美国，会发行特别版或收藏版邮票。
These are produced once and usually they mark a special occasion like the Olympics in 1996.
这些邮票只生产一次，通常是为了纪念特殊场合，比如1996年奥运会。
We had special edition stamps.
我们当时有特别版邮票。
Right.
对。
So these special edition objects are usually not used.
所以这些特别版物品通常不会被使用。
They're for collectors like the name says, right?
就像名字说的，它们是给收藏家的，对吧？
Collector's edition.
收藏版。
Right.
对。
So you plan to sell them later on or you collect them for yourself.
所以你打算以后卖掉它们，或者自己收藏。
They're not normal.
它们不是普通的。
Right.
对。
They don't really go up in value because they're very limited.
它们不会真正升值，因为非常限量。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
So collector's edition, special edition.
所以收藏版、特别版。
And now when they were talking about the porcelain dolls as well, it's pretty expensive, right?
现在，当他们谈到瓷娃娃时，也很贵，对吧？
Almost $200.
差不多200美元。
That's a really expensive doll.
那真是个很贵的娃娃。
And so one of the kids said, you know what?
然后其中一个孩子说，你知道吗？
I think mom and dad won't buy you that because it costs a pretty penny.
我觉得爸妈不会给你买那个，因为它花了一大笔钱。
A pretty penny.
一大笔钱。
This does not mean that the penny is beautiful.
这并不意味着那个便士很漂亮。
Right.
对。
A penny is a one cent coin in the United States.
便士是美国的一分钱硬币。
That means it's very, very low in value, the coin.
意思是这枚硬币价值非常非常低。
But a pretty penny is actually the opposite.
但“一大笔钱”实际上意思相反。
It means it's very expensive.
它表示非常昂贵。
So how would you use this in another example?
那你怎么在另一个例子中使用这个短语？
I've always wanted to buy a Ferrari, but man, Ferraris cost a pretty penny.
我一直想买一辆法拉利，但天啊，法拉利花一大笔钱。
Okay.
好的。
So you have to add the word cost before you say pretty penny, right?
所以你得在说“一大笔钱”之前加上“花”这个词，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
You can't say it is a pretty penny.
你不能说“它是一大笔钱”。
You have to say it costs a pretty penny or it's worth a pretty penny.
你得说“它花了一大笔钱”或“它值一大笔钱”。
Exactly.
完全正确。
It's worth a pretty penny.
它值一大笔钱。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
And for our last phrase, I think this one is a very good phrase because it describes
至于最后一个短语，我觉得这个短语很好，因为它描述了很多不同的夜光玩具。
a lot of different toys that glow in the dark.
夜光玩具。
Glow in the dark toys.
Okay.
好的。
So something that glows in the dark, the verb here is to glow, means that it can be seen
所以某种在黑暗中发光的东西，这里的动词是“发光”，意思是即使在黑暗中也能被看到。
even when it's dark.
即使在黑暗中。
Right.
对。
So for example, when I turn the lights off and I can see this yo-yo in my room, that
比如，当我关掉灯，能在房间里看到这个悠悠球，那就说明它是夜光的。
means it's glow in the dark.
意味着它在黑暗中发光。
It has light even in the dark.
它在黑暗中也有光。
Right.
对。
So there are a lot of different toys and things like this.
所以有很多不同的玩具和类似的东西。
Usually glow in the dark toys, they have a green glow, right?
通常夜光玩具会发出绿光，对吧？
They look green in the dark.
它们在黑暗中看起来是绿色的。
I used to have stars.
我以前有星星。
So they were stickers, star stickers, and I put them on my ceiling so that when I was
它们是贴纸，星星贴纸，我贴在天花板上，这样我躺在床上时就能看到它们，它们是夜光的。
in bed, I could look at them and they were glow in the dark.
所以当灯关掉时，我仍然有星星。
So when the lights were off, I still had stars.
你仍然能看到它们，对吧？
You can still see them, right?
所以是的，夜光。
So yeah, glow in the dark.
这是一种描述物品的方式，指你在黑暗中能看到的物体。
It's a way of describing an item, an object that you are able to see in the dark.
一种描述物品的方式，指你在黑暗中能看到的物体。
All right.
好的。
So that's all we have for you on language.
这就是我们关于语言部分的所有内容。
All right.
好的。
So that's all we have for you on Fluency Builder.
这就是我们关于流利度训练的所有内容。
When we go back, listen to the dialogue one last time, and we'll be back to talk some
我们回去后，再听一遍对话，然后我们会回来继续聊。
more.
海绵宝宝在简短消息后马上回来。
Spongebob Squarepants will be right back after these brief messages.
What's that on the horizon?
地平线上那是什么？
A pirate ship.
一艘海盗船。
Raid villages and find buried treasure with these new pirates Lego set.
用这套新海盗乐高套装，去袭击村庄、寻找埋藏的宝藏吧。
Build the ship and decide who rules the sea.
搭建这艘船，决定谁来统治海洋。
Har!
哈！
The new Play-Doh Sparkling Brights Precious Gem Brass.
新款培乐多彩泥闪亮宝石系列——珍贵宝石套装。
Make large colorful gems for you and your friends with five special molds.
用五个特殊模具，为你和朋友们制作色彩缤纷的大宝石。
Comes with the new Sparkling Brights Play-Doh Compound in four new colors.
附赠新款闪亮彩泥，有四种新颜色。
Treasure chest sold separately.
宝箱需单独购买。
Wow, mommy, can I get that for my birthday?
哇，妈妈，我生日能要那个吗？
Wolverine, Jean Grey, Rogue, and Professor X.
金刚狼、琴·葛蕾、小淘气和X教授。
Collect all four of these special edition collectible X-Men action figures and decide
收集全部四款特别版X战警可动人偶，决定
the future of the mutants in our world.
我们世界中变种人的未来。
No way!
不会吧！
I want Professor X!
我想要X教授！
The new collector's edition Nursery Rhymes Porcelain Dolls.
新款收藏版童谣瓷娃娃。
Little Bo Peep comes with her own shape and staff.
小波比带着她自己的羊和牧羊杖。
Her clothes are made with the finest fabrics and real Italian lace.
她的衣服由最优质的面料和真正的意大利蕾丝制成。
And her face has been hand painted by our finest artists.
她的脸由我们最优秀的艺术家手工绘制。
Only $199.
仅售199美元。
Oh, she's pretty.
哦，她真漂亮。
I've never had a porcelain doll before.
我以前从没有过瓷娃娃。
I doubt mom and dad will get you that for your birthday.
我怀疑爸妈不会在你生日时给你买那个。
She costs a pretty penny.
她可不便宜。
Plus, you'd most likely break her.
而且，你很可能把她弄坏。
What is better than a board?
有什么比一个棋盘游戏更好？
What is better than one board game?
Three board games in one.
三个棋盘游戏合为一体。
Enjoy playing chess and checkers on this side of the board.
在棋盘这一面玩国际象棋和跳棋。
And if you're looking for some more fun, flip it and play the classic game of Sorry.
如果你想找更多乐子，翻过来玩经典游戏“抱歉”。
That's ingenious!
太有创意了！
Why hasn't anyone thought of that before?
为什么以前没人想到这个？
Now you can take SpongeBob SquarePants wherever you go with the new SpongeBob SquarePants
现在你可以带着海绵宝宝去任何地方，用这款新款海绵宝宝
Glow in the Dark Yo-Yo.
夜光悠悠球。
And now, back to our show.
现在，回到我们的节目。
Alright so talking about toys, these are really interesting toys.
好了，说到玩具，这些真的很有趣。
Are there any specific toys that you had when you were growing up or that you really, really
你小时候有没有什么特别喜欢的玩具，或者你非常非常
liked?
喜欢的？
I had an amazing Brio train set.
我有一套很棒的Brio火车套装。
This was when I was young and a train set is basically like Legos with trains.
那是我小时候的事，火车套装基本上就像带火车的乐高。
So you build a track and you push the train around the track.
所以你搭建轨道，然后推着火车在轨道上跑。
And so I used to have a track that was as big as the living room.
我以前有一条和客厅一样大的轨道。
And my challenge, my goal was to use every single piece.
我的挑战，我的目标是用上每一块零件。
Which is very hard because some pieces don't fit with other pieces.
这很难，因为有些零件和其他零件不匹配。
And so that was my favorite toy because I got to be very creative.
所以那是我最喜欢的玩具，因为我可以很有创意。
And then you would turn on the train and it would go away.
然后你打开火车，它就会跑起来。
It wasn't electric.
它不是电动的。
So I had to push it myself.
所以我得自己推它。
What was your favorite toy?
你最喜欢的玩具是什么？
Actually when I was growing up I used to collect little toy cars.
其实我小时候喜欢收集小玩具车。
I had a lot of them.
我有很多。
Surprise!
惊喜吧！
I used to have a lot of little toy cars and I even had a little special, I don't know,
我有很多小玩具车，甚至还有一个特别的，我不知道，
like a box for them so I could see them.
像是个盒子，这样我就能看到它们。
And then as time went on I got to collect the scale cars, you know the ones that are
后来我开始收集比例模型车，你知道那种
1 to 10, 1 to 4.
1比10、1比4的。
Did you build them or did you buy them made?
你是自己拼装还是买现成的？
No, usually I bought them made.
不，我通常买现成的。
I actually tried the whole building model cars, model airplanes, but it's so hard.
我其实试过拼装模型车、模型飞机，但太难了。
Very hard.
非常难。
Even adults have a hard time with that.
连大人都觉得难。
It's very difficult.
非常困难。
So I don't know what type of kid actually does that when they're growing up.
所以我不知道哪种小孩小时候会做那种事。
But yeah, so many toys out there.
但没错，世上有这么多玩具。
So many people collect them, play with them.
这么多人收集它们、玩它们。
You have childhood toys that you're very fond of.
你童年时有些玩具让你非常怀念。
So that's what we want to know.
这就是我们想知道的。
What type of toy did you grow up with?
你小时候玩过什么类型的玩具？
What did you like to play with when you were a kid?
你小时候喜欢玩什么？
Or if you have kids, what toys do your kids like?
或者如果你有孩子，你的孩子喜欢什么玩具？
Because we're not too familiar with toys these days.
因为我们对现在的玩具不太熟悉。
We'd be curious to hear about those.
我们很好奇想听听那些。
That's right.
没错。
So we want to hear from you.
所以我们想听听你的意见。
Come to EnglishPod.com and we'll see everyone there.
来EnglishPod.com，我们会在那里见大家。
Bye.
再见。